<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Virtual Internships | Nhi (Chelsea) Le</title>
    <link>/tag/virtual-internships/</link>
      <atom:link href="/tag/virtual-internships/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Virtual Internships</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Virtual Internships</title>
      <link>/tag/virtual-internships/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>KPMG Data Analytics Virtual Internship</title>
      <link>/project/kpmg-vi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/kpmg-vi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The KPMG Data Analytics Virtual Internship Program offered by InsideSherpa has 3 modules:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt; 
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data quality assessment: involves assessment of data quality and completeness in preparation for analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;br&gt; 
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data insights: involves identifying high-values customers based on customers demographics and attributes. I used R for this task.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;br&gt; 
&lt;ol start=&#34;3&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data insights and presentation: producing data visualisations to present key insights and recommendations to the client. I used Tableau for this task.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantium Data Analytics Virtual Internship</title>
      <link>/project/quantium-vi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/quantium-vi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, I was invited to be a program tester for an exiciting data analytics virtual internship soon to be launched on InsideSherpa. To my complete surprise, this program is from Quantium - a renowned data science company recognised in Australia and globally. Ever since I started my first year at Monash, I have always had an immense passion for data analytics, and so naturally, being able to work at Quantium some day has been my biggest dream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This experience, therefore, was so rewarding and eye-opening for me. Not only was I among the first few people to experience the program prior to its launch day, I was also given the opportunity to provide suggestions on where and how the internship can be further improved. Many of my recommendations ended up being implemented by the InsideSherpa and Quantium teams, which is probably one of the proudest moments of my university years so far.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The program gave me invaluable insights on the type of work that an analyst does at Quantium. In particular, I was able to learn so much from how they tackle big and untidy datasets to produce commercial recommendations to the client. I hope to continue sharpening my data analytics and coding skills to hopefully, someday, be able to work at Quantium.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The materials (slides, videos) attached to this post are my attempts at the internship only. I will try and set aside some time to walk you through the suggested answers by Quantium as well, so make sure to keep an eye out for that if you are interested!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
